<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<addon
  id="pvr.dvbviewer"
  version="0.1.7"
  name="DVBViewer Client"
  provider-name="jdembski, A600">
  <requires>
    <c-pluff version="0.1"/>
  </requires>
  <extension
    point="xbmc.pvrclient"
    library_linux="XBMC_dvbviewer.pvr"
    library_osx="XBMC_dvbviewer.pvr"
    library_wingl="XBMC_dvbviewer_win32.pvr"
    library_windx="XBMC_dvbviewer_win32.pvr"
    library_android="libXBMC_dvbviewer.so"/>
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <summary lang="el">Frontend του XBMC για το DVBViewer</summary>
    <summary lang="en">XBMC's frontend for DVBViewer</summary>
    <description lang="en">DVBViewer Recording Service frontend; supporting streaming of LiveTV, Timers, Recordings &amp; EPG. For parsing the XML output from the RS webinterface it uses the xmlParser library developed by Frank Vanden Berghen (http://www.applied-mathematics.net/tools/xmlParser.html). Many thanks for this!&#10;</description>
    <disclaimer lang="be">This is unstable software! The authors are in no way responsible for failed recordings, incorrect timers, wasted hours, or any other undesirable effects..</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="ca">Això és programari inestable! Els autors no són en absolut responsables d'enregistraments fallist, temporitzadors incorrectes, hores tudades, o qualsevol altra efecte indesitjable...</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="cs">Tento software není stabilní. Autoři nejsou žádným způsobem zodpovědní za selhání při nahrávání, neplatné časovače, ztracený čas, či jakékoliv jiné nežádoucí události...</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="da">Dette er ustabilt software! Ophavsmændene er på ingen måde ansvarlige for fejlede optagelser, fejlagtige timere, spildte timer, eller andre uønskede konsekvenser.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="de">Diese Software ist noch in der Entwicklung! Die Autoren sind nicht für fehlgeschlagene Aufnahmen, falsche Timer, verschwendete Zeit oder andere ungewollte Effekte verantwortlich.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="el">Ασταθές πρόγραμμα! Οι δημιουργοί δεν είναι σε καμία περίπτωση υπεύθυνοι για αποτυχημένες εγγραφές, λανθασμένους χρονοδιακόπτες, χαμένες ώρες, ή κάθε είδους ανεπιθύμητα αποτελέσματα..</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="en">This is unstable software! The authors are in no way responsible for failed recordings, incorrect timers, wasted hours, or any other undesirable effects..</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="es">¡Este software es aún inestable! Los autores no son responsables en forma alguna por grabaciones fallidas, temporizaciones incorrectas, tiempo perdido o ningún otro efecto no deseado.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="es_AR">¡Este software es inestable! Los autores no se responsabilizan por grabaciones fallidas, temporizadores incorrectos, horas perdidas, o cualquier otro efecto no deseado..</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="es_MX">¡Esto es software inestable! Los autores no son de ninguna manera responsables por grabaciones fallidas, temporizadores incorrectos, horas perdidas o cualquier otro efecto no deseado...</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="fi">Tämä on epävakaa ohjelma! Ohjelman kirjoittavat eivät vastaa millään tavalla epäonnistuneista nauhoituksista, ajastimen väärästä toiminnasta, hukatusta ajasta tai muista ei-halutuista tapahtumista.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="fr">Logiciel en cours d'élaboration ! Les auteurs ne sont en aucun cas responsables de l'échec des enregistrements, minuteries défectueuses, temps perdu ou autres effets indésirables..</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="he">זוהי תוכנה בלתי יציבה!מחברי התכנה אינם אחראים להקלטות כושלות,מתזמני הקלטות שגויים,שעות מבוזבזות,או כל תוצאה בלתי רצויה...</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="hu">Ez nem stabil szoftver! A készítők nem vállalnak felelősséget, a hibás felvételért, rossz időzítésért, elvesztegetett időért...</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="is">Þetta er óstöðugur hugbúnaður! Höfundarnir eru á engann hátt ábyrgir fyrir misheppnuðum upptökum, röngum upptökutímum, klukkustundum sem að fóru í súginn eða nokkrum öðrum óæskilegum áhrifum.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="it">Questo software è instabile! Gli autori non sono in alcun modo responsabili per registrazioni fallite, timers incorretti, ore perse, o qualsiasi altro effetto indesiderato.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="ko">이 소프트웨어는 불안정합니다! 제작자는 녹화 실패, 부정확한 타이머, 시간 낭비 및 기타 예상하지 못한 결과에 대해 책임지지 않습니다..</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="lt">Tai yra nestabili programinė įranga! Autorius jokiu būdu neatsakingas už nepavykusius įrašus, neteisingus laikmačius, iššvaistytas valandas, ar nutikus kitiems nepageidaujamiems poveikiams ...[COLOR=red](xbmc.lt siūlo/rekomenduoja testuojant šį priedą persijungti į Anglų [orinali] kalbą)[/COLOR]</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="mk">Ова е нестабилен софтвер! Авторите на ниту еден начин не одговараат за неуспешни снимки, неточни тајмери, потрошени часови, или било кои други несакани ефекти.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="nl">Deze software is niet 100% stabiel! De auteurs zijn op geen enkele wijze aansprakelijk voor mislukte opnames, verspilde tijd, of enig ander ongewild neveneffect..</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="no">Dette er ustabil programvare! Skaperen har ikke på noen måte ansvar for feilede opptak, feile timere, bortkastede timer, eller andre uønskede effekter..</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="pl">To oprogramowanie jest niestabilne! Autorzy w żaden sposób nie odpowiadają za nieudane nagrania, źle działające wyłączniki czasowe, stracone godziny czy też jakiekolwiek inne niepożądane efekty.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="pt">Este é um software instável! Os autores não se responsabilizam por falhas nas gravações, temporizadores incorrectos, outro qualquer efeito não desejado...</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="pt_BR">Este é um software instável! Os autores não são responsáveis por falhas nas gravações, agendamentos incorretos, horas dispendidas, ou quaisquer outros efeitos indesejáveis</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="ru">Это тестовая программа! Авторы не несут ответственности за неудачные записи, неверные таймеры, потраченное время и прочие нежелательные эффекты..</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="sk">Tento softvér nie je stabilný! Autori nenesú žiadnu zodpovednosť za chybné nahrávky vysielania, nesprávne časovače alebo iné neželané udalosti spôsobené týmto softvérom..</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="sl">To je nestabilna programska oprema! Avtorji niso odgovorni za neuspela snemanja, nepravilne časovnike, zapravljen čas in katerikoli drug neželen učinek...</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="sv">Detta är ostabil mjukvara! Upphovsmännen är inte ansvariga för misslyckade inspelningar, inkorrekta timers, bortslösade timmar, eller några andra oönskade effekter..</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="zh">这是不稳定版的软件！作者不对录制失败、错误定时造成时间浪费或其它不良影响负责。</disclaimer>
    <platform>all</platform>
  </extension>
</addon>

